<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Networks | Grant Foster</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tag/networks/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tag/networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Networks</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Networks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tag/networks/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Ecological Interactions Across Geographic Ranges</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/intermod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/intermod/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Across their geographic ranges, potential symbionts may interact any place they co-occur, or they may interact in only a subset of these sites. As a result, the actual presence of an interaction may be the result of local environmental or ecological contexts. The occurrence of an interaction may be due to the presence or absence of alternative partners (e.g., species may only interact with low-quality partners only if high-quality partners are absent), or directly due to abiotic conditions (e.g., one species’ preferences for or phenological overlap with a potential partner may change as a function of temperature). Given the tight coupling between their interactions, we expect that phylogenetically specialized symbionts to have little deviation between the potential and realized geography of their interactions, while we expect phylogenetically generalist species to realize a proportionally smaller portion of their potential geography. To test this hypothesis, we use a distribution modeling framework to predict the geographic overlap of symbiotic species, and then compare that overlap to models explicitly trained on geographic records of their interactions. We apply this framework to large-scale floral visitation, frugivory, and host-parasite networks. We find that congruence between geographic overlap and realized interactions differs across network types, but is generally higher for more phylogenetically specialized symbionts. Our results highlight the role that local ecological and environmental contexts play in mediating facultative interspecific interactions, and ultimately the potential for changing environments to alter ecological network structures.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutualistic Network Assembly Across Space</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/metacon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/metacon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In nature, local species interaction networks are dynamic, changing in composition and structural properties as new species disperse to the area, existing species become locally extirpated, and as existing links rewire to form new associations or dissolve old ones. These local-scale changes have important impacts on regional-scale metacommunity structure and stability, and understanding the role biotic interactions play in mediating these processes can yield important insights into the maintenance of interaction network structure across scales. In order to help bridge this gap, we incorporate competitor-mediated dispersal (CMD) processes into a model of plant-pollinator network assembly across a spatially-explicit metacommunity. In addition to more broadly providing insight into feedbacks between biotic interactions and metacommunity dynamics within the context of mutualistic networks, we aim to answer the following research questions: 1) At the metacommunity scale, does the presence or strength of CMD processes tend to stabilize or destabilize population and community dynamics? 2) Do CMD processes allow the persistence of generalist species where they may be otherwise excluded? And 3) Do CMD processes, in concert with environmental heterogeneity, work to dampen or amplify spatial “hotspots” or “coldspots” of generalism?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link Prediction in Tropical Plant-Frugivore Interaction Networks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/fruglink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/fruglink/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The observed structure of a consumer-resource network consists of only a subset of potential links within that network. The true structure deviates from the metaweb of potential interactions due to stochastic assembly processes, while sampling effort limitations and error mean our observed network likely imperfectly represents this realized structure. Link prediction methods allow us to construct potential metawebs for a given empirical network. These predictions can guide targeted sampling of predicted links between rare species as well as give insight into potential interactions that may occur as species’ ranges shift. These interactions may be predicted using a variety of information types; understanding how different kinds of information compare in their ability to predict links between different types of nodes is important. To this end, we compare random-forest classifier models informed by combinations of phylogenetic structure, species traits, and latent network structure in their ability to predict interactions in a diverse network of fruiting plants and frugivorous birds in Brazil’s Atlantic forest.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes in Mutualistic Network Architecture in Response to Human Change</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anthropogenic disturbance and climate change impacts nearly all ecosystems on the planet through a number of mechanisms, one of which may be the altering of mutualistic interactions. Species turnover due to invasion and extinction, mismatches in species phenology, and other factors may fundamentally alter the architecture of mutualistic networks in many systems. These architectural changes may have predictable impacts on network features such as network stability or strength of hysteresis. Understanding how the structure of mutualistic networks are changing in general as well how these changes effect emergent network properties can allow us to better predict and manage threatened ecosystems.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
