<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | Grant Foster</title>
    <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disease Ecology Lab Materials</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/diseaseecology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/diseaseecology/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Spring of 2024, I was was enough to able to co-develop and co-teach Parasitology (BIOL 531/ENHS 661/EPID 661) alongside Tad Dallas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The course has an associated weekly 3 hour lab that I was able to create materials for, which I split between a mix of hands-on and computational labs using R. The syllabus for this course, as well as all student facing materials (both those created by myself and Tad) are publicly available on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dallaslab.github.io/diseaseEcology/syllabus/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;course website here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to implement any of these activities or assignments into you own courses! I&amp;rsquo;m also happy to provide instructor-facing implementation and grading notes for each of the labs as well; just send me an email!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R modules for Honors Ecology &amp; Evolution</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/h301/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/h301/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Fall 2023, I was able to be the teaching assistant for the honors section of Ecology and Evolution lab under &lt;a href=&#34;https://sc.edu/study/colleges_schools/artsandsciences/biological_sciences/our_people/directory/franklin_william.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Dr. Trey Franklin&lt;/a&gt;. A number of the labs associated with this course include analytical components that have historically been taught in R. However, for the honors section this year I instead included a (hopefully) gentle introduction to R, which students used throughout the semester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A zip file containing all the student-facing I created R materials and necessary associated data can be downloaded &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.com/uploads/BIOL301L_Materials.zip&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Feel free to adapt or use any of these materials in your own classes, or reach out if you have any ideas of questions!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
